alright guys a few people to get in here
I did put it on Twitter right sometime I
forget to put it on Twitter um so what I
want to show you all is this is a shelfs
copy so if you're not looking for
shelling during the wrong place but if
you're looking for shilling you're in
the right place because this is a shill
sculpey okay guys so
here in this box look at them look at
these beautiful very pandas they all
want homes they all want you to buy them
whether you buy them for $200 or as part
of the upgrade where you send back your
white panda and you get a gray panda
gray pandas are the highest quality
super high quality GPS
they have great GPS is inside them super
precision me ome chips very good very
good
same as Tesla the upgrade is $1.00 so
it's one of the dollars you said your
panda back when we get your panda yeah
yup it's still going on it's going on
until Friday we've shipped out our first
grade pandas from the upgrade so make
sure to get in today let me just show
you how well tested gray pandas are so
this is a testing rig these are the ones
here that failed testing this is our
testing right here for great patties so
you can see that we check to make sure
they all get GPS signal they all have
working can buses we basically make sure
everything about your gray pan to work
so when you get it you'll have a great
experience I just show you guys what the
test looks like on the computer so I
just go up here run gray test dot pi
yeah gray test all right let's see if
these ones pass oh yeah
op that all passed okay now it's gonna
test the can buses on the pandas - ah
you'll have to email support if you want
some special requests and those succeed
as well so these are the untested gray
pandas don't worry there's a whole lot
more of them - we'll just take a little
peek there and if you think that's it
wait'll you see just how many great
pandas we're doing we are moving weight
around here
so make sure to go to shop kamidana yeah
you know that you are a look you
kidnapped a bird you know that URL make
sure to go there is there a new revision
no it's the same revision well they're
all pretty good the newer ones are
probably a bit better tested but you
know that's how it is when you buy new
hardware but ya know they're there
good very high precision they come with
I don't have any right here but they
come with a great antenna they come with
a $50 antenna how do you initiate the
trade go on Twitter your left to scroll
back and find the link check out the pan
to upgrade your just ask on slack slack
that confidant I go they'll point you to
what I'm sure yeah so yeah check it out
these are these are the ones that failed
testing don't worry they won't be
shipped to you these all panas testing
so we could take them look we've moved
yellow caps for them right here
what's grape and to support like for
right-hand drive well that's why we
support so that's good yeah look at
those you're putting out on that
electric scooter it's it's Nick's
electric scooter actually hey scope is
remember when we had staples copies
that's a lie
but yeah guys that's all the shilling
I'm doing today this is a form to its
kind of man and he kind of used it it
makes things dirty
we can leave we'll leave we'll check out
the printer farm no scope Sunday but oh
yeah no we're having that indicator ya
know we'll add that indicator
yeah look at these look at the army oh
look at them great panting of Tanna box
look at these scrape and a antenna box
cacheable where's the fusion fusion but
yeah oh oh yeah miss I guess I guess it
won against chase works for us now so
that happened
all right scope ease there's a service
this is me make sure to go to shop
comedy I and buy our great panelists
today by thanks shells don't be good bye
bye